<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../resources/catalog.xsl'?>
<c:catalog xmlns="http://zero-install.sourceforge.net/2004/injector/interface" xmlns:c="http://0install.de/schema/injector/catalog"><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/APBuild.xml"><name>APBuild</name><summary>a suite of portability tools for developers</summary><description>
In the process of writing autopackage, we've also produced several standalone
tools, the apbuild programs, that are designed to help Linux developers write
better software that runs on a wider variety of distributions. They are
independent of autopackage itself: you can use them even if you don't provide
your software using the rest of our software.</description><homepage>http://autopackage.org/aptools.html</homepage><category>Development</category><icon href="http://autopackage.org/gnome-devel.png" type="image/png"/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/Blender.xml"><name>Blender</name><summary>a versatile 3D animation creation suite</summary><description>
Blender is a fully integrated 3D animation suite for use in animation, still
graphics, scientific and engineering visualization, and game content creation.

It includes tools for modeling, texturing (node based materials or uv mapped),
uv mapping, rigging and constraints, weight painting, particle systems,
simulation (fluids, physics, and soft body dynamics and an external crowd
simulator), rendering, node based compositing, and non linear video editing, as
well as an integrated game engine for real-time interactive 3D, and game
creation and playback with cross-platform compatibility.</description><homepage>http://www.blender.org</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/Blender.png" type="image/png"/><category>Video</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/Django.xml"><name>Django</name><summary>the Web framework for perfectionists with deadlines</summary><description>
Django is a high-level Python Web framework that encourages rapid development
and clean, pragmatic design.

Developed and used over two years by a fast-moving online-news operation, Django
was designed to handle two challenges: the intensive deadlines of a newsroom and
the stringent requirements of the experienced Web developers who wrote it. It
lets you build high-performing, elegant Web applications quickly.</description><homepage>http://www.djangoproject.com/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/LyX.xml"><name>LyX</name><summary>WYSIWYM(ean) document processor</summary><description>
LyX is an advanced open source document processor running on many Unix and some
non-Unix platforms. It is called a &quot;document processor&quot;, because unlike standard
word processors, LyX encourages an approach to writing based on the structure of
your documents, not their appearance. LyX lets you concentrate on writing,
leaving details of visual layout to the software.

LyX automates formatting according to predefined rule sets, yielding consistency
throughout even the most complex documents. LyX produces high quality,
professional output -- using LaTeX, an open source, industrial strength
typesetting engine, in the background.

With LyX, short notes or letters are a snap. LyX really shines, though, when
composing complex documents like technical documentation, doctoral theses and
conference proceedings.</description><homepage>http://www.lyx.org</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/LyX.png" type="image/png"/><category>Office</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/Mutt.xml"><name>Mutt</name><summary>text-based mail client</summary><description>
Mutt is a sophisticated text-based Mail User Agent.</description><homepage>http://www.mutt.org/</homepage><category>Network</category><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/Mutt.png" type="image/png"/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/Subversion.xml"><name>Subversion</name><summary>advanced version control system</summary><description>
Subversion, also known as svn, is a version control system much like the
Concurrent Versions System (CVS). Version control systems allow many individuals
(who may be distributed geographically) to collaborate on a set of files
(typically source code). Subversion has all the major features of CVS, plus
certain new features that CVS users often wish they had.

This package includes the Subversion client (svn), tools to create a Subversion
repository (svnadmin) and to make a repository available over a network
(svnserve).</description><homepage>http://subversion.tigris.org</homepage><category>Development</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/Tgif.xml"><name>Tgif</name><summary>interactive 2-D drawing tool</summary><description>
Tgif is an interactive drawing tool that allows the user to draw and manipulate
objects in the X Window System.</description><homepage>http://bourbon.usc.edu/tgif/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/Tgif.png" type="image/png"/><category>Graphics</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/UserModeLinux.xml"><name>UserModeLinux</name><summary>run Linux inside itself</summary><description>
User-Mode Linux is a safe, secure way of running Linux versions and Linux
processes. Run buggy software, experiment with new Linux kernels or
distributions, and poke around in the internals of Linux, all without risking
your main Linux setup.

User-Mode Linux gives you a virtual machine that may have more hardware and
software virtual resources than your actual, physical computer. Disk storage for
the virtual machine is entirely contained inside a single file on your physical
machine. You can assign your virtual machine only the hardware access you want
it to have. With properly limited access, nothing you do on the virtual machine
can change or damage your real computer, or its software.</description><category>System</category><homepage>http://user-mode-linux.sourceforge.net</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/UserModeLinux.png" type="image/png"/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/XdgUtils.xml"><name>XdgUtils</name><summary>cross-desktop integration tools</summary><description>
Xdg-utils is a set of command line tools that assist applications with a variety
of desktop integration tasks. About half of the tools focus on tasks commonly
required during the installation of a desktop application and the other half
focuses on integration with the desktop environment while the application is
running. Even if the desktop components of your application are limited to an
installer, configuration or management tool, Xdg-utils provides you with an easy
way to enhance the usage experience of your customers by improving the
integration of these components in the user's environment. Best of all, Xdg-
utils is provided as open source and free of charge.</description><homepage>http://portland.freedesktop.org</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libapr1.xml"><name>libapr1</name><summary>the Apache Portable Runtime Library</summary><description>
APR is Apache's Portable Runtime Library, designed to be a support library that
provides a predictable and consistent interface to underlying platform-specific
implementations.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libaprutil1.xml"><name>libaprutil1</name><summary>the Apache Portable Runtime Utility Library</summary><description>
APR is Apache's Portable Runtime Library, designed to be a support library that
provides a predictable and consistent interface to underlying platform-specific
implementations.

APR Util is a utilities library implemented on top of apr, providing database
access, xml parsing, and other useful functionality.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libaudio2.xml"><name>libaudio2</name><summary>the Network Audio System (NAS)</summary><description>
The Network Audio System was developed by NCD for playing, recording, and
manipulating audio data over a network. Like the X Window System, it uses the
client/server model to separate applications from the specific drivers that
control audio input and output devices.

This package contains the nas library (libaudio), needed for both remote and
local output.</description><homepage>http://radscan.com/nas.html</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libcomerr2.xml"><name>libcomerr2</name><summary>common error description library</summary><description>libcomerr is an attempt to present a common error-handling mechanism to
manipulate the most common form of error code in a fashion that does not
have the problems identified with mechanisms commonly in use.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libdb4.4.xml"><name>libdb4.4</name><summary>Berkeley v4.4 Database Libraries</summary><description>
This is the runtime package for programs that use the v4.4 Berkeley database
library.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libdb4.6.xml"><name>libdb4.6</name><summary>Berkeley v4.6 Database Libraries [runtime]</summary><description>This is the runtime package for programs that use the v4.6 Berkeley
database library.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libenchant1.xml"><name>libenchant1</name><summary>a wrapper library for various spell checker engines</summary><description>
Enchant is a generic spell checking library which uses existing spell checker
engines such as ispell, aspell and myspell as its backends.

Enchant steps in to provide uniformity and conformity on top of these libraries,
and implement certain features that may be lacking in any individual provider
library.</description><homepage>http://www.abisource.com/projects/enchant/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libexpat1.xml"><name>libexpat1</name><summary>XML parsing C library</summary><description>
This package contains the runtime, shared library of expat, the C library for
parsing XML.</description><homepage>http://expat.sourceforge.net</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libgcrypt11.xml"><name>libgcrypt11</name><summary>LGPL Crypto library - runtime library</summary><description>libgcrypt contains cryptographic functions. Many important free
ciphers, hash algorithms and public key signing algorithms have been
implemented:
arcfour, blowfish, cast5, DSA, DSA2, des, 3DES, elgamal, MD5, rijndael,
RMD160, RSA, SEED, SHA1, SHA-384, SHA-512, twofish, tiger.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libgnutls13.xml"><name>libgnutls13</name><summary>the GNU TLS library</summary><description>
gnutls is a portable library which implements the Transport Layer Security (TLS)
1.0 and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) 3.0 protocols.

Currently gnutls implements:

- the TLS 1.0 and SSL 3.0 protocols, without any US-export controlled algorithms

- X509 Public Key Infrastructure (with several limitations).

- SRP for TLS authentication.

- TLS Extension mechanism

This package contains the runtime libraries.</description><homepage>http://www.gnu.org/software/gnutls/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libgnutls26.xml"><name>libgnutls26</name><summary>the GNU TLS library - runtime library</summary><description>gnutls is a portable library which implements the Transport Layer
Security (TLS) 1.0 and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) 3.0 protocols.

Currently gnutls implements:
 - the TLS 1.0 and SSL 3.0 protocols, without any US-export
   controlled algorithms
 - X509 Public Key Infrastructure (with several limitations).
 - SRP for TLS authentication.
 - TLS Extension mechanism

This package contains the runtime libraries.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libgpg-error0.xml"><name>libgpg-error0</name><summary>library for common error values and messages in GnuPG components</summary><description>Library that defines common error values for all GnuPG
components. Among these are GPG, GPGSM, GPGME, GPG-Agent, libgcrypt,
pinentry, SmartCard Daemon and possibly more in the future.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libgucharmap4.xml"><name>libgucharmap4</name><summary>unicode browser widget library</summary><description>
The libgucharmap library contains a Unicode browser widget; it is most
prominently used by the &quot;gucharmap&quot; program.

This package contains the shared library.</description><homepage>http://gucharmap.sourceforge.net/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libkeyutils1.xml"><name>libkeyutils1</name><summary>Linux Key Management Utilities (library)</summary><description>Keyutils is a set of utilities for managing the key retention facility in the
kernel, which can be used by filesystems, block devices and more to gain and
retain the authorization and encryption keys required to perform secure
operations.

This package provides a wrapper library for the key management facility system
calls.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libkrb53.xml"><name>libkrb53</name><summary>MIT Kerberos runtime libraries</summary><description>
Kerberos is a system for authenticating users and services on a network.
Kerberos is a trusted third-party service. That means that there is a third
party (the kerberos server) that is trusted by all the entities on the network
(users and services, usually called &quot;principals&quot;).

This is the MIT reference implementation of Kerberos5.

This package contains the runtime libraries used by applications and Kerberos
clients.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libldap-2.4-2.xml"><name>libldap-2.4-2</name><summary>OpenLDAP libraries</summary><description>These are the run-time libraries for the OpenLDAP (Lightweight Directory
Access Protocol) servers and clients.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libldap2.xml"><name>libldap2</name><summary>run-time libraries for the OpenLDAP servers and clients</summary><description>
These are the run-time libraries for the OpenLDAP (Lightweight Directory Access
Protocol) servers and clients.</description><homepage>http://www.openldap.org/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libmysqlclient15off.xml"><name>libmysqlclient15off</name><summary>MySQL database client library</summary><description>MySQL is a fast, stable and true multi-user, multi-threaded SQL database
server. SQL (Structured Query Language) is the most popular database query
language in the world. The main goals of MySQL are speed, robustness and
ease of use.

This package includes the client library.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libneon26.xml"><name>libneon26</name><summary>an HTTP and WebDAV client library</summary><description>
Neon is an HTTP and WebDAV client library, with a C language API.

WARNING: THE NEON API IS NOT YET STABLE.

Provides lower-level interfaces to directly implement new HTTP methods, and
higher-level interfaces so that you don't have to worry about the lower-level
stuff.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libneon27-gnutls.xml"><name>libneon27-gnutls</name><summary>An HTTP and WebDAV client library (GnuTLS enabled)</summary><description>neon is an HTTP and WebDAV client library, with a C language API.

WARNING: THE NEON API IS NOT YET STABLE.

Provides lower-level interfaces to directly implement new HTTP
methods, and higher-level interfaces so that you don't have to
worry about the lower-level stuff.

Current features:
  * High-level interface to HTTP and WebDAV methods (PUT, GET, HEAD, etc.)
  * Low-level interface to HTTP request handling, to allow implementing
    new methods easily.
  * persistent connections
  * RFC2617 basic and digest authentication (including auth-int, md5-sess)
  * Proxy support (including basic/digest authentication)
  * SSL/TLS support using GnuTLS (including client certificate and thread
    safety support)
  * Generic WebDAV 207 XML response handling mechanism
  * XML parsing using the expat or libxml parsers
  * Easy generation of error messages from 207 error responses
  * WebDAV resource manipulation: MOVE, COPY, DELETE, MKCOL.
  * WebDAV metadata support: set and remove properties, query any set ofi
    properties (PROPPATCH/PROPFIND).
  * autoconf macros supplied for easily embedding neon directly inside an
    application source tree.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libpq4.xml"><name>libpq4</name><summary>PostgreSQL C client library</summary><description>
libpq is a C library that enables user programs to communicate with the
PostgreSQL database server. The server can be on another machine and accessed
through TCP/IP. This version of libpq is compatible with servers from PostgreSQL
7.3 to 8.1.

This package contains the run-time library, needed by packages using libpq.

PostgreSQL is an object-relational SQL database management system.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libpq5.xml"><name>libpq5</name><summary>PostgreSQL C client library</summary><description>libpq is a C library that enables user programs to communicate with
the PostgreSQL database server. The server can be on another machine
and accessed through TCP/IP. This version of libpq is compatible
with servers from PostgreSQL 8.2 or later.

This package contains the run-time library, needed by packages using
libpq.

PostgreSQL is an object-relational SQL database management system.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libqt-mt3.xml"><name>libqt-mt3</name><summary>Qt GUI Library (threaded runtime version)</summary><description>
This is the Trolltech Qt library, version 3. It's necessary for applications
that link against the libqt-mt.so.3, e.g. all KDE3 applications.</description><homepage>http://www.trolltech.com</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libsasl2-2.xml"><name>libsasl2-2</name><summary>Cyrus SASL - authentication abstraction library</summary><description>This is the Cyrus SASL API implementation, version 2.1.

SASL is the Simple Authentication and Security Layer, a method for
adding authentication support to connection-based protocols. To use
SASL, a protocol includes a command for identifying and
authenticating a user to a server and for optionally negotiating
protection of subsequent protocol interactions. If its use is
negotiated, a security layer is inserted between the protocol and the
connection. See RFC 2222 for more information.

Any of: ANONYMOUS, CRAM-MD5, DIGEST-MD5, GSSAPI (MIT or Heimdal
Kerberos 5), NTLM, OTP, PLAIN, or LOGIN can be used. If you intend to
use this package on a server that provides SASL authentication, then
you must install some of the libsasl2-modules* packages.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libserf-0-0.xml"><name>libserf-0-0</name><summary>high-performance asynchronous HTTP client library</summary><description>serf library is a C-based HTTP client library built upon the Apache
Portable Runtime (APR) library. It multiplexes connections, running the
read/write communication asynchronously. Memory copies and
transformations are kept to a minimum to provide high performance
operation.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libsqlite3-0.xml"><name>libsqlite3-0</name><summary>SQLite 3 shared library</summary><description>SQLite is a C library that implements an SQL database engine.
Programs that link with the SQLite library can have SQL database
access without running a separate RDBMS process.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libssl0.9.8.xml"><name>libssl0.9.8</name><summary>SSL shared libraries</summary><description>
libssl and libcrypto shared libraries needed by programs like apache-ssl,
telnet-ssl and openssh.

It is part of the OpenSSL implementation of SSL.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libsvn1.xml"><name>libsvn1</name><summary>shared libraries used by Subversion</summary><description>
This package includes shared libraries to manipulate Subversion (svn)
repositories and working copies.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libuuid1.xml"><name>libuuid1</name><summary>universally unique id library</summary><description>libuuid generates and parses 128-bit universally unique id's (UUID's).
See RFC 4122 for more information.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/libxml2.xml"><name>libxml2</name><summary>GNOME XML library</summary><description>XML is a metalanguage to let you design your own markup language.
A regular markup language defines a way to describe information in
a certain class of documents (eg HTML). XML lets you define your
own customized markup languages for many classes of document. It
can do this because it's written in SGML, the international standard
metalanguage for markup languages.

This package provides a library providing an extensive API to handle
such XML data files.

This feed is deprecated; use http://repo.roscidus.com/lib/xml2 instead.
</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2007/3rd-party/mysql-common.xml"><name>mysql-common</name><summary>MySQL database common files</summary><description>MySQL is a fast, stable and true multi-user, multi-threaded SQL database
server. SQL (Structured Query Language) is the most popular database query
language in the world. The main goals of MySQL are speed, robustness and
ease of use.

This package includes files needed by all versions of the client library
(e.g. /etc/mysql/my.cnf).</description></interface></c:catalog>
<!-- Base64 Signature
iQEzBAABCgAdFiEE2pglrsrQiXV82r2OBxM/lsp02LoFAl4R0VAACgkQBxM/lsp02Lr2zggAjHb7
qLNvx+TWb6uJcVS4JmqSrK6qiwqxKJBCqZmEnYsy6WkRy3sYhijNDAu2Cy4DHMOXWkB5B0z5wl/3
y6roWcyanqUUILNQca/AM3JipDnqGlVJfe1/r/r09viygP/PIOG4vRs8gfZuC9Mf2C5SxzCR4V0g
V2W5jQQJVFiX7T0l5+C1YeO/+cUheKFVDHNrWRVSBqHxooDlOl6j2uTEZilknrcNhDQSSsAzskq+
xjXNje7n3QdiffLm83mczb7FAy/oK3Pn4rOBwDlgRaJHygVaCmokVhTjzod1jm3z7Ko1wsF817x8
6jimcrqsZ4vGF2s9UBEZJe7e9g4wV3meyg==

-->
