<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../resources/catalog.xsl'?>
<c:catalog xmlns="http://zero-install.sourceforge.net/2004/injector/interface" xmlns:c="http://0install.de/schema/injector/catalog"><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/Lincity.xml"><name>Lincity</name><summary>city simulation game</summary><description>
Lincity is a city simulation game. You are required to build and maintain a
city. You must feed, house, provide jobs and goods for your residents. You can
build a sustainable economy with the help of renewable energy and recycling, or
you can go for broke and build rockets to escape from a pollution ridden and
resource starved planet, it's up to you.</description><homepage>http://lincity.sourceforge.net/</homepage><category>Game</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/OpenEuclide.xml"><name>OpenEuclide</name><summary>2D geometry software</summary><description>
OpenEuclide is a 2D geometry software: figures are defined dynamically by
describing formal geometrical constraints. This project is a basic tool for
educational or modeling purpose. It is distributed under the GNU GPL licence,
free and multi-platform (up to now, GNU and windows).</description><homepage>http://coulon.publi.free.fr/openeuclide</homepage><category>Education</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/SCOURGE.xml"><name>S.C.O.U.R.G.E.</name><summary>rogue-like game in the tradition of NetHack and Moria</summary><description>
S.C.O.U.R.G.E. is a rogue-like game in the fine tradition of NetHack and Moria.
It sports a graphical front-end, similar to glHack or the Falcon's eye. I tried
to design the 3D UI as a best of both worlds from old to new: It lets you rotate
the view, zoom in/out, view special effects, etc. On the other hand I've always
liked the old-school isometric games like Exult or Woodward</description><homepage>http://scourge.sourceforge.net/</homepage><category>Game</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/Stellarium.xml"><name>Stellarium</name><summary>a beautiful night sky simulator</summary><description>
Stellarium is a free open source planetarium for your computer. It shows a
realistic sky in 3D, just like what you see with the naked eye, binoculars or a
telescope.

It is being used in planetarium projectors. Just set your coordinates and go.</description><homepage>http://www.stellarium.org/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/Stellarium.png" type="image/png"/><category>Education</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/Supertux.xml"><name>Supertux</name><summary>2D jump'n run sidescroller game</summary><description>
SuperTux is a classic 2D jump'n run sidescroller game in a style similar to the
original SuperMario games. The Milestone1 release of SuperTux features 9
enemies, 26 playable levels, software and OpenGL rendering modes, configurable
joystick and keyboard input, new music and completly redone graphics. Together
with a little story, we hope to provide a good gaming experince with this first
Milestone release.</description><homepage>http://supertux.berlios.de/</homepage><category>Game</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/Abiword.xml"><name>abiword</name><summary>AbiWord Word Processor</summary><description>
AbiWord is a lightweight word processing application.</description><category>Office</category><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/abiword.png" type="image/png"/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/armagetronad.xml"><name>armagetronad</name><summary>a Tron clone in 3D</summary><description>
&quot;A Tron clone in 3D&quot;.

This has been the tagline of Armagetron, since, well, a very long time, and is
probably the shortest and most accurate description possible. Tron was an arcade
game based on the movie of the same name, release by Disney in 1982. The
original game consisted of 4 sub-games, the only one of concern is the 'Light
Cycles' one, in which the player uses a left/right joystick to control a 'Light
Cycle' which leaves a wall behind it wherever the cycle it goes, turning only at
90 degree angles. The player must then get the AI to crash into their wall while
avoiding hitting the AI's own wall themselves. Those were the humble beginnings
of Armagetron Advanced's game play, which has now blossomed into 16 player
mayhem, with highly advanced AI, network game play, and of course all in a 3D
environment.</description><homepage>http://www.armagetronad.net/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/armagetronad.png" type="image/png"/><category>Game</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/gtkdc.xml"><name>gtkdc</name><summary>client for the Direct Connect network</summary><description>
A client for the Direct Connect peer-to-peer network inspired by DC++.</description><homepage>http://www.gtkdc.org/</homepage><category>Network</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/opencity.xml"><name>opencity</name><summary>OpenCity Simulation Game</summary><description>
  OpenCity is a full 3D city simulator game project. It is written in standard
  C++ with OpenGL and SDL from scratch. It is not intended to be a clone of any
  famous city simulator from Max*s. So, if you are looking to download a free
  SimCity 4 like, please forget OpenCity. I work on it at my spare time, I
  really meant it &quot;my spare time&quot;!
  </description><homepage>http://www.opencity.info/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/opencity.png" type="image/png"/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/sear.xml"><name>sear</name><summary>Sear - a client for Worldforge</summary><description>
Sear is a client for MMORPGs using the Worldforge system.</description><category>Game</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/autopackage/vdrift.xml"><name>vdrift</name><summary>VDrift</summary><description>
VDrift is a realistic racing simulation with drifting in mind</description><category>Game</category></interface></c:catalog>
<!-- Base64 Signature
iQEzBAABCgAdFiEE2pglrsrQiXV82r2OBxM/lsp02LoFAl4R0VAACgkQBxM/lsp02LrLGwgAhTxc
K2TjmvkLi3xxaRgX0c5ZG1yiFdwS2QDq9eWYGw03yofuw59ERaq1yPFiJY7WRewCuUq9KAmL0WQW
6k6BiTvqtvfdZI63mGFrIWICFGhY+7vqmfG500vFKD+IiW/7KsE2WiDdQBKVw/q1zJQaA09nDMQ+
CL97xld/0l2AZm4nhHWLHmhPL16dl1BRC4B6aSeLFvms07fG7pvEW9POsTuwi5ydBNhOdKcEfUmL
raffJ5k6cxHVobb658D4bh3gBDUlSLlxfEVFOs3dB215GmhX5vzkTCqg7fllRI+cqWRdQm4zcLmf
o/bTp8iExFNa86sRNxidqnZA7xBf4jciNA==

-->
