<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../resources/catalog.xsl'?>
<c:catalog xmlns="http://zero-install.sourceforge.net/2004/injector/interface" xmlns:c="http://0install.de/schema/injector/catalog"><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/0compile.xml"><name>0compile</name><summary>create a binary release from source code</summary><description>
0compile creates a binary from source code, either for your own use or ready for
publishing on the web through Zero Install. It can use Zero Install to download
any build dependencies (compilers, header files, build tools, etc).

This is useful if there is no binary for your platform, or if you wish to modify
the program in some way.

If plash is installed, it is used to sandbox the build so that it can't
accidentally modifiy any files outside of the build directory.

For a full tutorial, see 0compile's homepage.</description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0compile/</homepage><category>Development</category><needs-terminal/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/0publish"><name>0publish</name><summary>utility to make creating injector interfaces easier</summary><description>
0publish makes creating and modifying injector interface files easier. It can
create a new commented template for you or edit an existing one.

Various editing operations are available, the most basic being to let you edit
it in your preferred text editor. It automatically removes the signature when
loading an interface and creates a new one when writing it back out. It will
also validate the new version before saving it.

A tutorial on 0publish can be found at http://0install.net/injector-
packagers.html.</description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0publish/</homepage><needs-terminal/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/ATK-dev"><name>ATK-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling ATK applications</summary><description>
These are the ATK header files. They are required when compiling applications
that use the ATK library. ATK is an Accessibility Toolkit.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/GLib-dev"><name>GLib-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling GLib applications</summary><description>
These are the GLib header files. They are required when compiling applications
that use the GLib library.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/GLibmm-dev.xml"><name>GLibmm-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling C++ GLib applications</summary><description>
These are the glibmm header files. They are required when compiling C++
applications that use the GLib library.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/GTK-2.4.xml"><name>GTK-2.4</name><summary>set up a GTK 2.4 build environment</summary><description>
This program runs a command in an environment with PKG_CONFIG_PATH set to
include the location of the GTK 2.4 and related library headers. By default, it
runs /bin/sh to give you a shell.

Typical usage is to run this and then configure and build your program from the
new shell. The resulting binary should work on all systems with GTK 2.4 and
later.

Note: if you build your program using Zero Install then it's easier to just add
the GTK dependencies to the source interface file.</description><icon href="https://0install.net/2006/icons/gtk-logo.png" type="image/png"/><category>Development</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/GTK-dev"><name>GTK-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling GTK applications</summary><description>
These are the GTK header files. They are required when compiling applications
that use the GTK+ library.</description><icon href="https://0install.net/2006/icons/gtk-logo.png" type="image/png"/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/GTKmm-dev.xml"><name>GTKmm-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling C++ GTK applications</summary><description>
These are the glibmm header files. They are required when compiling C++
applications that use the GTK, ATK or Pango libraries..</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/Pango-dev"><name>Pango-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling Pango applications</summary><description>
These are the Pango header files. They are required when compiling applications
that use the Pango library. Pango is a library for laying out and rendering of
text, with an emphasis on internationalization.</description></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/interfaces/ZeroInstall-GUI.xml"><name>ZeroInstall-GUI</name><summary>graphical interface for the Zero Install injector</summary><description>
The Zero Install GUI displays a window showing which versions of various
components will be used when running a program, and allows you to alter various
policy settings to affect the selection process. You can use this to mark
particular versions of libraries as preferred, bugggy, etc.</description><homepage>https://0install.net/</homepage></interface></c:catalog>
<!-- Base64 Signature
iQEzBAABCgAdFiEE2pglrsrQiXV82r2OBxM/lsp02LoFAl/4VM8ACgkQBxM/lsp02LopLQf+Ns+9
TwMj+nUz4Ld+IrA91Lzr+11pnjiLWr28ORC6zKCcGHg7ciS3XP3cf8xN2Nk1H/16rB+Kma3ScJYM
QBvTLVmUNvJDGrYc/SI5g1vLLD9ka8nMUbVpWZRmyjfXPHk50p6lbxDKv235Ld1JsUrCasFBWEHc
fE4b9HUeT1DLvnwu9LfuaZVLZQDHyw1wtFFGlji1tPKBypR8E81NyC/GdUehF2i8QZcv5A81kTdd
Dh2zCdhQXdkJKkngtg/b+7ulp4iE4YjzgIWzKYbel8/r8ccf4ywuSAFHOh0TyYmi6oZIyhKW7sSn
LKzCS86bgmtIIPeXqKuKlwd5UC/Tg6TkmA==

-->
