<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../resources/catalog.xsl'?>
<c:catalog xmlns="http://zero-install.sourceforge.net/2004/injector/interface" xmlns:c="http://0install.de/schema/injector/catalog"><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/0share.xml"><name>0share</name><summary>peer-to-peer sharing of Zero Install packages</summary><description>
Zero Install is a decentralised installation system. Meta-data about each
package is published in a &quot;feed&quot; file.

Before downloading a package over the internet, 0launch can check to see if any
nearby machines have a copy, and get it from them instead if so. This will
normally be much faster. The secure hash from the feed is used to check that the
software hasn't been modified.</description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0share/</homepage><category>Network</category><needs-terminal/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/0test.xml"><name>0test</name><summary>test Zero Install programs</summary><description>
Use 0test to run the unit tests for a Zero Install program. You can use this to
test released versions or developer snapshots. You can give a selection of
versions to test, and you can test against different versions of dependencies to
create a matrix of test results.</description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0test/</homepage><category>Development</category><needs-terminal/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/ZeroInstall-GUI.xml"><name>ZeroInstall-GUI</name><summary>graphical interface for the Zero Install injector</summary><description>
The Zero Install GUI displays a window showing which versions of various
components will be used when running a program, and allows you to alter various
policy settings to affect the selection process. You can use this to mark
particular versions of libraries as preferred, bugggy, etc.

This program is run automatically by the '0launch' command. If you want to add
an installer to your desktop menus, you want something like Zero2Desktop
instead.</description><homepage>https://0install.net/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/deb2zero.xml"><name>deb2zero</name><summary>create Zero Install feeds from Debian packages</summary><description>
Zero Install is a decentralised installation system. Meta-data about each
package is published in a &quot;feed&quot; file. The Zero Install client reads these feeds
files and downloads and runs the programs. The feed files can be created
manually (e.g. using 0publish or 0publish-gui). However, Debian packages already
contain much of the required information. This program extracts the information
in an existing Debian package and uses it to generate the feed.</description><homepage>https://0install.net/deb2zero.html</homepage><category>Development</category><needs-terminal/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/libglade-dev.xml"><name>libglade-dev</name><summary>headers for compiling Glade applications</summary><description>
These are the Glade header files. They are required when compiling applications
that use the Glade library.</description><homepage>http://glade.gnome.org</homepage><category>Development</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/libxml2-dev.xml"><name>libxml2-dev</name><summary>headers for libxml2</summary><description>
Libxml2 is the XML C parser and toolkit developed for the Gnome project (but
usable outside of the Gnome platform), it is free software available under the
MIT License. XML itself is a metalanguage to design markup languages, i.e. text
language where semantic and structure are added to the content using extra
&quot;markup&quot; information enclosed between angle brackets. HTML is the most well-
known markup language. Though the library is written in C a variety of language
bindings make it available in other environments.</description><homepage>http://xmlsoft.org/</homepage><category>Development</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2008/interfaces/lzmadec.xml"><name>lzmadec</name><summary>small and fast LZMA decoder</summary><description>
lzmadec is a small and fast decoder for LZMA compressed files. It is intended to
work as a drop-in replacement for lzma in situations where available disk space
is limited, only decoder is needed and the data can be decompressed from the
standard input to the standard output. This has been achieved by simply ignoring
all command line arguments except --help.</description><homepage>http://tukaani.org/lzma/</homepage><category>Utility</category></interface></c:catalog>
<!-- Base64 Signature
iQEyBAABCgAdFiEE2pglrsrQiXV82r2OBxM/lsp02LoFAl/4VM8ACgkQBxM/lsp02LpH9Af41DAn
0eD0KsmQAYhp6Uo9EDf/TKceKRNSREbj6mM6PDgnia6iqM4w5plshSsNXhKsiYgYfIDyBjACgLyS
rCP0UXdFga2LCurnoNA+8k+oafMKVfsQ4KR4UbONVvUXI9FrqKVLbtVjjLBV1Jv8RvqpaP7/JSeq
lgpRiGUf2kdoWADeHKpQfsYwKGL3sdv+Q8sGPxZbgG3qE+kszFGEy3PySWdeed405lewkFIJfPED
34hdtvf7UaE+SXLRR+oywp5ZwLwskxEOlP8eMqy8036WXT401xcwQmEOAFKqYTqtZ9UJbOmRlDke
q/0GoV7aB5bPcuLcEGRLJtGoW/e+P1Xo

-->
