<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../resources/catalog.xsl'?>
<c:catalog xmlns="http://zero-install.sourceforge.net/2004/injector/interface" xmlns:c="http://0install.de/schema/injector/catalog"><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/3rd-party/Freetype2.xml"><name>Freetype2</name><summary>free, portable library for digital typography</summary><description>
FreeType 2 is a high-quality and portable font engine that is capable of
supporting several font formats (be they bitmapped or scalable) through a simple
and uniform interface. Its design is modular and allows independent &quot;font
driver&quot; modules to be added, even at runtime, to support additional formats. It
also provides a high-quality anti-aliasing renderer, an innovative auto-hinting
engine, and support for the following font formats: TrueType Type1, CID-Type 1,
Multiple Masters Type 1 OpenType/CFF, pure CFF, and CEF Windows FNT/FON.</description><homepage>http://www.freetype.org/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/3rd-party/GDC.xml"><name>GDC</name><summary>D Compiler for GCC</summary><description>
GDC is a D language front end for the GNU Compiler Collection. It supports a
number of targets and nearly all features of Digital Mars D.

D is a systems programming language. Its focus is on combining the power and
high performance of C and C++ with the programmer productivity of modern
languages like Ruby and Python. Special attention is given to the needs of
quality assurance, documentation, management, portability and reliability.

D is statically typed, and compiles direct to native code. It's multiparadigm:
supporting imperative, object oriented, and template metaprogramming styles.
It's a member of the C syntax family, and its look and feel is very close to
C++'s. For a quick feature comparison, see this comparison of D with C, C++, C#
and Java.</description><homepage>http://dgcc.sourceforge.net/</homepage><category>Development</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/3rd-party/Inkscape.xml"><name>Inkscape</name><summary>an SVG-based vector drawing application</summary><description>
Inkscape is an Open Source vector graphics editor, with capabilities similar to
Illustrator, Freehand, CorelDraw, or Xara X using the W3C standard Scalable
Vector Graphics (SVG) file format. Supported SVG features include shapes, paths,
text, markers, clones, alpha blending, transforms, gradients, patterns, and
grouping. Inkscape also supports Creative Commons meta-data, node editing,
layers, complex path operations, bitmap tracing, text-on-path, flowed text,
direct XML editing, and more. It imports formats such as JPEG, PNG, TIFF, and
others and exports PNG as well as multiple vector-based formats.

Inkscape's main goal is to create a powerful and convenient drawing tool fully
compliant with XML, SVG, and CSS standards. We also aim to maintain a thriving
user and developer community by using open, community-oriented development.</description><homepage>http://inkscape.org/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/tests/Inkscape.png" type="image/png"/><category>Graphics</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/3rd-party/PySol.xml"><name>PySol</name><summary>a collection of more than 200 solitaire card games</summary><description>
PySol is an exciting collection of more than 200 solitaire card games. Its
features include support for lots of distinct games, very nice look and feel,
multiple cardsets and table tiles, sound and background music, unlimited undo &amp;
redo, load &amp; save games, player statistics and log files, hint system, demo
games, support for user written plug-ins, integrated HTML help browser and lots
of documentation.

Among the supported games are classics like Aces Up, Baker's Game, Canfield,
FreeCell, Forty Thieves, Golf, Klondike, Pyramid, Scorpion, Spider, Yukon, and
many more...

PySol is copyrighted OpenSource software distributed under the terms of the GNU
General Public License.

PySol is written in 100% pure Python</description><homepage>http://www.pysol.org/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/tests/pysol.png" type="image/png"/><category>Game</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/3rd-party/SCons.xml"><name>SCons</name><summary>a software construction tool</summary><description>
SCons is a software construction tool (build tool substitute for Make)
implemented in Python. It features a modular build engine that can be embedded
in other software. SCons configuration files are Python scripts that call the
build engine API.

It can scan files to detect dependencies automatically and maintain a global
view of all dependencies in a build tree, and uses MD5 signatures to detect
changed file contents reliably. Timestamps can be used if you prefer. SCons also
supports parallel builds and is easily extensible through user-defined builder
and scanner objects.</description><homepage>http://www.scons.org/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/tests/scons-logo.png" type="image/png"/><category>Development</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/2006/3rd-party/XaraXtreme.xml"><name>Xara Xtreme</name><summary>cross-platform vector artwork and photocomposition package</summary><description>
XaraLX is a vector graphics and photocomposition program. It is primarily a
vector graphics program, but it also handles photos and drawings. It has an
easy-to-use and easy-to-learn approach.</description><homepage>http://www.xaralx.org/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/XaraXtreme.png" type="image/png"/><category>Graphics</category></interface></c:catalog>
<!-- Base64 Signature
iQEzBAABCgAdFiEE2pglrsrQiXV82r2OBxM/lsp02LoFAl4R0VAACgkQBxM/lsp02LpjlAf9H8QT
W8RCSVp2Jx0acDJlsAi/nSg9U8S81zdWLxcqAvMRiNvnd+iCmtISQcomh38uWKrTFQjR4flSrMT0
G7gjyVI4bwlF7pP3UUbLM1VoTO4XlihSIJlxt9mJbUYOk0DUb7c6BHkhLEyR8QKG9P7n2Q1ix+9p
09z+m3ZlFIB8xwW3487FBrolJObwEDmyvxjsxKwVzBzQ3D1sIEEJIyuP/DPchsVy7pF54tuGnd8P
DnB4bvf8Vm/9gcMLY4Zphgpe7w2Z+IUlVjmFiOeRvFP+TVxvJAvsZCPdxgEwIM5pzsziFec9cjMo
sToSWeDocvkRPDnFHSszoGa0Eq3v51o5pQ==

-->
