<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../resources/catalog.xsl'?>
<c:catalog xmlns="http://zero-install.sourceforge.net/2004/injector/interface" xmlns:c="http://0install.de/schema/injector/catalog"><interface uri="http://0install.net/tools/0export.xml"><name>0export</name><summary>create self-installing bundles for distribution on CD</summary><description>
It is sometimes useful to bundle a program and its libraries together
on a CD (for example) so that it can be used on machines without a network
connection, or where the network is very slow. It is also useful for archival
purposes, in case the original web-sites supplying required libraries become
unavailable.

0export takes the URI of a program and creates a &quot;setup.sh&quot; file; a self-
extracting archive containing everything needed to run the program. This file
can be executed on a machine without a network connection to install or run the
program.

Unlike the bundles created by the related zero2bundle program, programs
installed using setup.sh are added to the Zero Install cache and are therefore
still shared between users, and will get updates over the web where possible.</description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0export/</homepage><category>Development</category><needs-terminal/></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/tools/0install.xml"><name>0install</name><summary>decentralised installation system</summary><description>
Zero Install is a decentralised cross-platform software installation
system available under the LGPL. It allows software developers to publish
programs directly from their own web-sites, while supporting features familiar
from centralised distribution repositories such as shared libraries, automatic
updates and digital signatures. It is intended to complement, rather than
replace, the operating system's package management. 0install packages never
interfere with those provided by the distribution.
</description><homepage>https://0install.net/</homepage><icon href="https://0install.net/feed_icons/ZeroInstall.png" type="image/png"/><category>System</category></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/tools/0repo.xml"><name>0repo</name><summary>manage a repository of 0install feeds</summary><description>
    0repo allows a group of developers to publish a set of feeds. It can be
    used by a single developer, generating a set of static files to publish on
    a web-server, or as a service which accepts signed updates from a group
    of developers.
  </description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0repo/</homepage></interface><interface uri="http://0install.net/tools/0template.xml"><name>0template</name><summary>utility to make creating feeds easier</summary><description>
    0template takes a template XML file (e.g. with place-holders for the version),
    fills in the place-holders, and then fills in everything else it can. For example,
    it will download the archive, fill in the size, calculate the digests, etc.
  </description><homepage>https://docs.0install.net/tools/0template/</homepage><needs-terminal/><entry-point binary-name="0template" command="run"/></interface></c:catalog>
<!-- Base64 Signature
iQEzBAABCgAdFiEE2pglrsrQiXV82r2OBxM/lsp02LoFAl/4VM8ACgkQBxM/lsp02Lqavgf/eVSM
Mb1g9qd57qTni8h5qbCzYlc41UpNRGAE+CMINnr9kfT0b0O/C/3OXbmojB8eUal9J6+wAYcEVKW4
QbGc+gGNzJuWBfFqjUEeBFb7l2skNNT8OWTgyD9GK4bRtTaSSc5J2tzG945sZuPjBe27+6e8+vZw
v21Zgp5Jb1vxcrG+NQO1qBHZSlsxfajhG7Lg/Feejs7se0HFVRGCwxo38g77zg3+LxDEh0ARi+wj
1cVECbwq2E2DhPJ7el41FhC6OISXjIuFHvR9RTTkCQzuTr/q/xsWdkE6lUY5PJDT+Quvj1ED4y44
+Som8qunbMr9haeJ79OO60T4biwrlkRmNQ==

-->
